Previously on the show. The goats thought the stars took the tourists' gems,
上集說到 小羊以為星星們拿走了遊客的寶石
and a series of misunderstandings ensued.
而產生了一系列的誤會
Meanwhile, Wolffy invented a transmission device...
另一邊，灰太狼發明了一個傳送器
to summon the seven evil wolves to catch the goats.
把七大惡狼召喚過來抓羊
But they still didn't manage to succeed.
可最後還是徒勞無功
What's going to happen next?
接下來會怎麼樣呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Sleeping Starry Town"
《奇幻天空島之》
Baby, do you not like how it tastes?
寶寶是不是不喜歡 這個奶糊的口味啊？
You refuse to eat it but open your mouth. Do you like it or not?
不吃又張嘴 這是喜歡啊，還是不喜歡？
Baby, did you not sleep well?
寶寶，你沒睡好嗎？
Baby, did you eat the energizing herb?
寶寶，你該不會是吃了提神草了吧？
What's an energizing herb?
什麼是提神草？
The energizing herb can awaken a comatose patient.
提神草擁有喚醒昏睡病人的功能
But if a healthy person eats it,
如果把提神草給沒有病的人吃了
he won't be able to sleep.
就會失眠
It was just coffee that you drank. Thank goodness.
原來你只是喝了咖啡，還好…
But I still can't sleep!
還是睡不著啊！
At least he didn't eat the energizing herb. Poor baby.
幸好不是吃了提神草，真可憐
I must put him to sleep.
我一定要想辦法讓寶寶睡個好覺
Baby, I know what I can do to help you sleep.
寶寶，我想到辦法讓你可以睡覺了
Grandpa Elder, what's that?
長老爺爺，這是什麼呀？
That's a calming flower. It can put you to sleep.
可以幫助入睡的安神花
But there's no flower.
可是沒有花呀
Don't worry.
別急
We just have to water it, and it'll grow very quickly.
給它澆點水，它就會快速生長
Its fragrance puts people to sleep.
並散發出陣陣幽香讓人沉睡
Water it now then.
那趕快澆吧
Wait,
等一下
if we water it now, we'll fall asleep, too.
要是現在澆水，我們也會睡著的
Water it after we leave.
等我們走了，你再澆水吧
Elder, it's time for our rehearsal.
長老，是時候去排練了
Sweet dreams, baby.
祝你有個好夢，寶寶
I'm going, too. Goodnight, Chief.
那我也出去了，村長，晚安
Who put the durian in the fridge?
誰把榴蓮放冰箱了呀？
How does this pose look?
這個造型怎麼樣？
It's the same as last time.
這是上一次的造型
What about this?
這樣呢？
I think it looks exactly the same.
好像，沒有什麼不一樣
Why aren't you helping out?
你們怎麼不幫忙啊？
We are. We made these for their performance.
我們在幫忙啊 這些都是給星星們表演用的
Look how nicely I made it.
你看我折得多好
Isn't it too small?
會不會小了一點？
-Use your powers to enlarge it. -Okay.
-用你的能力把星星變大一點 -好
Paddi, don't move around!
懶羊羊，你別亂動啊！
Sorry. Do it again.
對不起，你再射一次吧
Something smells good. Oh...
好香啊，喝啊…
Why am I so sleepy, too?
我怎麼也想睡…
Dad, you haven't finished the story yet.
爸爸，故事還沒說完
All right...
好…
The prince passed out because he hadn't eaten in a long time.
因為太久沒吃東西了，王子暈倒了
The princess cried sad tears.
公主流下了難過的淚水
And a miracle happened. The prince woke up.
奇蹟出現了，王子醒了過來
Tears can wake people up!
原來眼淚可以把人叫醒
Son, this is just a fairy tale. Tears are not medicine.
兒子，這只是童話，眼淚又不是藥
They can't wake anybody up.
怎麼可能喚醒別人呢？
Ha-choo!
哈啾！
I'm getting a cold. We'll finish the story next time.
爸爸感冒了，故事下次再繼續說
But I want to know how it ends now!
可是我現在就想知道結局！
In the end, the prince still doesn't get to eat the goats.
結局就是，王子還是吃不到羊
Just like us. We have to starve.
像我們家一樣，要繼續挨餓
Wolnie, don't cry. I'll get you some food now.
紅紅別哭啊，我這就去給妳找吃的
Wolnie, why did you fall asleep?
紅紅，妳怎麼睡著了？
Sleep then. I'll go get some goats.
你們先睡，我這就去抓羊去
Don't they have a performance? Why are they all sleeping?
不是應該在表演的嗎？ 怎麼全睡在這了？
The goats are here too? Great.
小羊也在這啊？太好了
Wait, this doesn't feel right.
不對啊，好像有點不對勁啊
Wo... Wolffy.
灰…灰太狼
What's wrong with you guys?
你們怎麼了？
Everyone's fallen asleep because of the calming flower.
大家都因為安神花，睡過去了
Is that why Wolnie and Willie fell asleep?
難道紅紅和小灰灰 也是因為這樣才睡著的？
You must wake us up in an hour,
你一定要在一個小時內叫醒我們
or things will be bad.
否則，後果很嚴重
Bad? How bad?
有什麼後果呀？
What will happen? Tell me!
會有什麼後果呀？快告訴我
Oh, right. Please take my laundry in.
對了，幫我收一下衣服
Wake up! My wife and son are asleep! What should I do?
快醒醒！我老婆孩子都睡著了 要怎麼辦啊？
Also, turn off the lights for me. Don't waste electricity.
還有要記住，幫我關燈，不要浪費電
What should I do now? What should I do?
現在該怎麼辦啊？ 我應該做些什麼呢？
Slowy?
慢羊羊？
Why aren't you affected?
你怎麼就沒事呢？
You're fine because you're wearing a mask?
你戴著口罩所以沒事？
What should we do now?
那現在怎麼辦啊？
The energizing herb.
提神草…
If we find it, we can wake Wolnie and Willie up?
只要找到它 紅紅和小灰灰就會醒過來
Go look for it then!
那趕緊去找啊！
No, I must control myself for my wife and son's sake.
不行，為了老婆和兒子，我一定要忍
Don't worry. This is a life-and-death issue. I won't eat you.
放心，人命關天，我是不會吃你的
Why do you keep staring at me?
你幹麼老是瞪著我呢？
It's a misunderstanding.
誤會…
We only have less than an hour. Let's go.
我們只有不到一小時的時間了 快點出發吧
I really want to eat him.
好想吃啊
Oh, no! It's been 20 minutes already!
糟糕，已經過了20分鐘了
We need to look harder!
繼續找！
Where is this energizing herb?
這提神草究竟在哪呢？
Fried lamb.
爆炒羊肉
Yummy!
美味啊！
Ouch!
好疼啊
I was just yawning.
我…我只是打個哈欠
I wasn't trying to eat you.
真的沒想吃你
I need to control myself. I'll eat him with Wolnie after waking her up.
我要忍住 要吃也要等到救醒了老婆一起吃
If you keep doing this, I might not be able to control myself anymore.
你要再這樣我真的忍不住了
Wolnie, son, there's hope!
老婆兒子有救了
Wolnie, Willie. I'm here to save you.
紅紅、兒子，我來救你們了
Willie...
小灰灰…
Things will be bad...
後果很嚴重…
Oh, no. I came too late.
完了…我來晚了
Wolnie! My son!
紅紅！兒子！
I'm sorry!
我對不起你們啊
Dad?
爸爸？
Wolnie! Son! You're awake!
紅紅、兒子！你們怎麼醒了？
Did my tears of love save you?
難道是我愛的眼淚？
So fairy tales are real.
原來童話是真的
Oh, the goats and the stars won't wake up without my tears.
對了，小羊和星星們 沒有我的眼淚是醒不了的
I finally have my chance.
終於有機會了
Wolffy!
灰太狼！
What are you doing?
你要幹什麼？
I'm just playing with the baby.
我…我這是在跟寶寶玩呢
I thought you've all been poisoned?
你們不是中毒了嗎？
How did you wake up without my tears?
沒有我的眼淚，你們怎麼醒了？
The calming flower isn't poisonous. Its effect just wore off.
安神花又沒有毒 藥效過了自然就會醒啊
What?
什麼？
But didn't you say if I didn't wake you up in an hour, things will be bad?
但你不是說，如果不在一個小時內 叫醒大家，後果會很嚴重嗎？
Wake us up in an hour, or things'll be bad.
一小時之內叫醒我們 否則後果很嚴重
It is bad!
當然嚴重了！
We missed the show The Boy Who Loves Stars with Flat-beak Allen in it.
扁嘴倫主演的 《愛看星的少年》都播完了
How's that not bad?
難道還不嚴重嗎？
What? Why?
你…為什麼？
Shh. I think he's really tired.
看來是太累了
Let him sleep. Shh.
讓他好好睡睡吧
TO BE CONTINUED 0001 DAY FROM SETTING SAIL
（未完待續 距離啟航還剩1天）